You wanna buy a watch?
This is maid of honor,
Amy Farrah Fowler...
(Amy(into a mini-cam):)...bringing you the wedding activities
just weeks out from the big day.
(Amy(into a mini-cam):)Let's check in with a beautiful,
radiant young woman...
(Amy(into a mini-cam):)...and her friend
who's about to get married.
(Amy(into a mini-cam):)Ladies, can you tell us
what you're doing?
Um, these are gift bags we're gonna put
in the hotel rooms of our guests.
(Bernadette:)This is a map of Pasadena,
this is a list of local restaurants.
(Bernadette:)Then for Howie's relatives,
we have antihistamines, antacids...
(Bernadette:)...and medicine
for diarrhea and constipation.
Ha, we labeled them "stop" and "go."
(Amy:)All right, pivoting to the big question.
(Amy:)Bernadette, on your wedding night,
you'll be consummating your marriage.
(Amy:)What do you think your first sexual position
will be as husband and wife?
(Bernadette:)Amy, please.
(Amy:)Keeping in mind that whoever's on top
may set the tone for the marriage.
(Penny:)Okay, show's over.